Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 21, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Search for Economic Security: America's Evolving Pattern of Family Security from Colonial Times to the Present, 1966; Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Author: Health Insurance Institute
- Box: 21, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Rupert Hughes Discusses How We Live, 1945; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: NBC
    Notes: February 24, 1945
  - Item 2: Class Friction and Formal Education, 1945; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: Fred G. Clark
    Notes: January 27, 1945
  - Item 3: Growth, Wages, Money, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: Dennis Robertson
  - Item 4: Something is Happening in Roman Catholicism, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: William Petrek
    Notes: July-September 1964
  - Item 5: Economics, 1950; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: John M. Amiss
  - Item 6: Economy and Society, 1955; Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: Wilbert E. Moore
  - Item 7: How We Live, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Author: Fred G Clark & Richard Stanton Rimanoczy
- Box: 21, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: International Economic Organizations & Terms, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Author: International Chamber of Commerce
- Box: 21, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Professor Strotz on a Specification Error, 1960; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Author: W.M. Gorman
    Notes: December 1960
  - Item 2: Notes on Jorgenson's Model, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Author: M. McManus
  - Item 3: Numbers and Size in Cournot Oligopoly, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 1961
  - Item 4: Cross Section and Time Series Estimates of the Accelerator - A Synthesis, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Author: A.A. Walters
  - Item 5: Two Papers Arising Out of Arrow's Article in the R.E.S. on Logarithmic Demand Functions, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Economies of Scale in the Aggregate Production Function, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: The Switching Problem in the Theory of Capital, 1962; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Two Papers on Multiple Programming, 1962; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Author: V. Mukerji
  - Item 9: The CES or 'SMAC' Production-Function when there are More than Two Inputs, 1962; Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Box: 21, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Introduction to Sources of Economic Data, 1966; Publication (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 20, 1966
  - Item 2: Principles of Collective Bargaining, 1948; Publication (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Author: Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers
    Notes: March 1948
- Box: 21, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Growth Rate Tables, 1966; Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Author: H.T. Burley
- Box: 21, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Use of Instructional Materials in Introductory Courses in the State University of New York, 1968; Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Author: J. Woodrow Sayre
  - Item 2: The Teaching of Economics in Latin America, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Author: Pan American Union
  - Item 3: Soviet Teaching and Research in Economics, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Economic Ideas and Concepts, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Economics in the School Curriculum, 1957; Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Author: Marion Daugherty
- Box: 21, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Paperbound Books in Economics, 1967; Publication (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Paperbound Books in Economics, 1965; Publication (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Paperbound Books in Economics, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Box: 21, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Helping Yourself to Understand Economics, 1947; Publication (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: A Glossary of Economic Terms, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Box: 21, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Seven Americans in Ecuador, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 24)
    Notes: November 11-25, 1961
- Box: 21, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Adult Education in the Public Schools, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
    Author: National Association of Public School Adult Educators
  - Item 2: Educationally Deficient Adults, 1965; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: New Directions in Programming for University Adult Education, 1957; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
    Author: Peter E. Siegle & James B. Whipple
    Notes: May 1957
  - Item 4: When You're Teaching Adults, 1959; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Adult Education, 1955; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
    Author: Robert A. Luke
  - Item 6: In-Service Training for Teachers of Adults, 1961; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: The Case for Adult Education, 1959; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Factors Associated with the Achievement of Adult Students, 1964; Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
    Author: King M. Wientge & Philip H. DuBois
- Box: 21, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Adult Education in a Changing Africa, 1954; Publication (Box 21, Folder 26)
    Author: David & Helen Kimble
    Notes: December 10-23, 1954
- Box: 21, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Selected References on Adult Education, Publication (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Box: 21, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Survey of Adult Education, 1965; Publication (Box 21, Folder 28)
    Author: Canada Dominion Bureau of Statistics
    Notes: 1964-65
  - Item 2: A Report to the Canadian People on Manpower Development, Publication (Box 21, Folder 28)
    Author: The Canadian Association for Adult Education
- Box: 22, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Conspectus to the Self-Study Project of University College: The University of Chicago, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Author: Robert M. Roth
- Box: 22, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Regional Mid-Career Education, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Author: Metropolitan Fund, Inc.
- Box: 22, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Federal Support for Adult Education, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Author: Adult Education Association
- Box: 22, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Adult Education in Citizenship in Postwar Germany, 1954; Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Author: Alice Hanson Cook
- Box: 22, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Higher Education Services to Adult Education in New York State, 1948; Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Author: Lester Dix
    Notes: December 1, 1948
- Box: 22, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Ambrose Caliver, Adult Educator and Civil Servant, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: Walter G. Daniel & John B. Holden
  - Item 2: Education of the Adult Migrant, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Continuing Learner, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults
  - Item 4: Research Arrangements Within University Adult Education Divisions, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: Alan B. Knox
  - Item 5: Creativity Research and its Implications for Adult Education, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: Jane C. Zahn
  - Item 6: New Directions in Degree Programs Especially for Adults, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: A.A. Liveright & Roger DeCrow
  - Item 7: A Proposed Program of Mid-Career Education for Public Adminstrators in Metropolitan Areas, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Author: Frederick C. Mosher
- Box: 22, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: College Without Classes, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: University-Sponsored Executive Development Programs in the Public Service, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Author: Ward Stewart
    Notes: May 11, 1966
  - Item 3: Review of Educational Research, 1950; Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Author: American Educational Research Association
  - Item 4: Plan Postwar Jobs - Now, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Box: 22, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Studies in Comparitive Education, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Box: 22, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Education in Asian Countries: An Introductory Reading and Buying Guide for Undergraduate Colleges and Libraries, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Author: Hyman Kublin
  - Item 2: Selected Bibliography on Education in Southeast Asia, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Box: 22, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Education in Bulgaria, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Box: 22, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report of the California Assembly Interim Committee on Education, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Author: California Assembly Interim Committee on Education
- Box: 22, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Children of Misfortune, 1954; Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Author: Shirley E. Greene
    Notes: May 1954
  - Item 2: Guide to Organization and Administration of Migrant Education Programs, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Author: Colorado State Department of Education
- Box: 22, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Education in Chile, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Box: 22, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Education for Freedom and World Understanding, 1962; Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 26-28, 1962
- Box: 22, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Review of Current Literature on Work Experience Programs, 1949; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Author: Lloyd W. Johnson & William H. Roe
    Notes: May 23, 1949
  - Item 2: Education Through Work Experience, 1948; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Part-Time Day Education for the Adolescent, 1942; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Author: British Association for Commercial & Industrial Education
    Notes: September 29, 1942
  - Item 4: Young Workers and Their Education, 1943; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Notes: April 15, 1943
  - Item 5: First Memorandum on Education of Young Employees in Industry, 1944; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: The Concerns and Expectations of Prospective Participants in Directed Work Experience Programs, 1967; Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Author: Harold R. Cushman, Charles W. Hill, John K. Miller
- Box: 22, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Student Workers in New York State, 1945; Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Author: New York State Division of Women, Child Labor and Minimum Wage
  - Item 2: Developing Work-Study Programs for Potential Dropouts, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Box: 22, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: School-and-Work Programs, 1947; Publication (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. Office of Education
- Box: 22, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Education in Czechoslovakia, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Box: 22, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Research in the Economics of Higher Education: Progress and Problems, 1962; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: Alice M. Rivlin
  - Item 2: OECD at Work for Science and Education, 1972; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Achieving Nationwide Educational Excellence, 1968; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: Leon H. Keyserling
  - Item 4: Raising the School-Leaving Age, 1951; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: I.L. Kandel
  - Item 5: The Effect of Education on the Earnings of Blacks and Whites, 1969; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: Randall D. Weiss
  - Item 6: Human Capital Intensity, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: Gerard K. Boon
  - Item 7: A Preliminary Study on Economics of Employment & Higher Education in Iran, 1969; Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Author: A. SH. Shaheen
    Notes: September 15-20, 1969
- Box: 22, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Manpower as an Asset in a Growth Economy, 1970; Publication (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Author: Joseph Hunt
    Notes: December 9, 1970
- Box: 22, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Projection of Manpower: Post-Elementary Education, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Author: State of Israel Ministry of Labour
- Box: 22, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Investment and Return: Public Education - New York State, 1967; Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Box: 22, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Use of the Dictionary of Occupational Titles to Estimate Educational Investment, 1968; Publication (Box 22, Folder 23)
    Author: Sidney A. Fine
- Box: 22, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Long Road to College: A Summer of Opportunity, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 24)
    Author: The Rockefeller Foundation
    Notes: Spring 1965
- Box: 22, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Education in France, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Box: 22, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Federal Role in Education, Publication (Box 22, Folder 26)
    Author: Congressional Quarterly Service
- Box: 22, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Report of the United States Education Mission to Germany, 1946; Publication (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Box: 22, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Next Steps in Education, 1949; Publication (Box 22, Folder 28)
    Author: Fabian Society
  - Item 2: The Years of Crisis, Publication (Box 22, Folder 28)
    Author: Labour Party's Study Group on Higher Education
- Box: 22, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Retooling for Higher Education, Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: The Needs of New Jersey in Higher Education, 1970; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
    Notes: 1962-1970
  - Item 3: Impact of College, 1960; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Advanced Standing, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: 1070-71 Upward Bound Guidelines, 1969; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: The Master Plan, Five Years Later, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
    Author: Coordinating Council for Higher Education
  - Item 7: Survey of State Legislation Relating to Higher Education, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Attitudes of Liberal Arts Faculty Members, 1960; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
    Author: Paul L. Dressel & Margaret F. Forimer
  - Item 9: Increasing Opportunities in Higher Education for Disadvantaged Students, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Higher Education Amendments of 1968, Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
    Notes: September 25, 1968
  - Item 11: Campus Unrest at Cornell, 1969; Publication (Box 22, Folder 29)
    Notes: September 5, 1969
- Box: 22, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Higher Education, Human Freedom and the Humanities, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 30)
    Author: Lucy W. Cole
  - Item 2: Education and the State, Publication (Box 22, Folder 30)
    Author: New York State Regents Advisory Committee on Educational Leadership
- Box: 22, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Report of Financial Statistics of Institutions of Higher Education, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Financing an Undergraduate Education, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Financing a Graduate Educaion, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Box: 22, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: National Higher Technical Education in Indonesia: Recent Trends, 1960; Publication (Box 22, Folder 32)
    Notes: October 1960
- Box: 22, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Higher Education in the Phillipines, 1961; Publication (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Box: 22, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Current Situation in Latin American Education, 1962; Publication (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Box: 22, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Survey of State Legislation Relating to Higher Education, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Survey of State Legislation Relating to Higher Education, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Legislation Concerning Education and Training, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: Maximum Basic Grants, 1965; Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: College and University Reports, 1968; Publication (Box 22, Folder 35)
    Notes: July 11, 1968
- Box: 22, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Higher Education and Research in the Netherlands, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 36)
    Author: Netherlands Universities Foundation for International Co-Operation
- Box: 22, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Regents Plan for Postwar Education, 1944; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Basic Issues in Secondary Education, 1945; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
    Author: New York State Education Department
  - Item 3: Education and the 1967 Constitutional Convention, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Federally-Assisted Manpower Development Programs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: A Decade of Development in Education, 1964; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 6: Major Recommendations of the State Board of Regents for Legislative Action, 1966; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Item 7: New York State University Official Fall Enrollment; Institutional Data, 1963; Publication (Box 22, Folder 37)